描述图像中灰度级的一种非常有用和简洁的方法是使用a
A very useful and concise way of describing the grey levels within an image is using a
工具称为直方图。在这里，我有一个人为的低分辨率
tool called a histogram. Here I have a contrived and low resolution
图像，其中像素灰度值在0（黑色）和10（白色）之间变化。
image, where the pixel grey values vary between 0, which is black, and 10, which is white.
我们可以将直方图过程视为排序过程。我要去拿
We can consider the histogramming process as a sorting process. I am going to take the
第一个像素，其灰度值为6，我将把它放入垃圾箱
first pixel, which has got a grey scale value of 6, and I am going to drop it into the bin
对于值为6的像素。我将采用下一个有值的像素
for pixels with a value of 6. And I am going to take the next pixel which has got a value
10，我打算将它放入bin中，以获得值为10的像素，依此类推。
of 10, and I am going to drop it into the bin for pixels of value of 10, and so on.
我们一直重复这个过程，直到我们为其中的所有像素着色
And we repeat this process on and on until we have coloured all of the pixels in the
图片。我们有这个直方图。一目了然
image. And we have this histogram. At a glance this
直方图告诉我们关于图像的一些非常有趣的事情。如果所有像素都是
histogram tells us some very interesting things about the image. If all of the pixels are
在直方图的左侧，这告诉我们它是一个非常暗的图像。反过来，
at the left-hand side of the histogram, this tells us that it is a very dark image. Conversely,
如果所有像素都在直方图的右侧，这告诉我们
if all of the pixels are at the right-hand side of the histogram, this tells us that
这是一个非常明亮的形象。您很可能遇到直方图。
it is a very bright image. You have very likely encountered histograms.
它们通常显示在相机的取景器中。我们在这里看到的是
They are commonly displayed in the viewfinder of a camera. What we are seeing here is the
iPhone相机应用程序的取景器，我们可以在显示屏上看到直方图。
viewfinder of an iPhone camera app and we can see the histogram here on the display.
直方图的左侧对应于暗像素，右侧对应于右侧
The left-hand side of the histogram corresponds to the dark pixels, and the right-hand side
直方图的对应于亮像素。如果我将相机从此视图移动到下方
of the histogram corresponds to bright pixels. If I move the camera from this view to down
在我的办公桌下面，一切都很暗，我们可以看到有越来越多的人
underneath my desk where it is all very dark, we can see that there are an increasing number
场景中的暗像素。当我从桌子下面拿起相机并指出时
of dark pixels in the scene. As I bring the camera up from underneath the desk and point
它在窗外非常明亮，我们看到像素的分布更加移动
it out the window where it is very bright, we see the distribution of pixels moving more
朝着直方图的明亮端。如果我重复这个过程，但这次我有
towards the bright end of the histogram. If I repeat the process, but this time I have
相机设置为自动曝光控制，现在发生的是内部的软件
the camera set to automatic exposure control, what happens now is that the software within
相机试图保持直方图平衡。它试图保持均匀的混合
the camera is trying to keep the histogram balanced. It is trying to keep an even mixture
暗像素和亮像素，使平均值位于中间的某个位置。和
of dark pixels and bright pixels, so that the average is somewhere in the middle. And
这一次的行为是完全不同的，当我们在桌子底下看时，我们可以看到
the behaviour this time is quite different, when we look under the desk, we can see the
电线和地毯。
wires and the carpet.
当我们向窗外望去时，我们现在可以清楚地看到外面的世界。
When we look out the window, we can now quite clearly see the world outside.